Hold on a second.
等一下
Nice.
好球…
I got you something.
有东西给你
What's this?
这什么东西？
Eight hundred and twelve bucks.
812块钱
Didn't Big Leon tell you? It's a thousand...
我不知道老李跟你怎么说的 跟我过夜…
...to have me for the whole night.
…可要一千大洋才够
What's this for?
这是干什么呀？
Well,I'm making money now.
我现在有赚钱了
I'm paying you back for headshots, electric bills,all that pizza....
这是要还你帮我付的电费 跟数不清的披萨的钱
I love you,man.
我爱你
Well,thanks,man. Now I can get my pony.
谢了，老兄 我有钱可以买小马了
This is a little extra something for...
这是我小小的心意…
...always being there for me.
…谢谢你平日的照顾
Wow,I don't know what to say.
我不晓得该说什么了
What do you say?
怎么样？
I don't know.
我不知道
It's a bracelet.
这是个手镯吧？
Isn't it? It's engraved,too. Check it out.
上头还刻了字，你看看
"To my best bud."
“我的好兄弟”
Thanks,best bud.
谢了，好兄弟
Put it on.
戴上去啊
Now?
现在吗？
No,it should be saved for a special occasion.
不…这么美的东西 应该留到特殊的场合再戴
No,that's the beauty part. It goes with everything.
不…妙就妙在这里 这配什么都好看
When you put this on, you're good to go.
老兄，你戴起来简直好看啊
Oh,man!
天啊
You are so wearing that bracelet!
真是太配你了
I so am!
可不是嘛！
Any idea what this will do for your sex life?
你知道这对你的性生活 有什么样的影响吗？
It might slow down at first,but...
刚开始时说不定会让我慢半拍
...once I'm used to the extra weight, I'll be back on track.
等到习惯这个重量之后 就会让我重振雄风了
The One With the Prom Video
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河马压缩制作 本字幕为河马根据R3DVD OCR得来
六人行 第2季 第14集 高中舞会录影带
-This all looks good. -Great.
看起来很好 那就好了
If I want to call for a reference on your last job...?
如果我要打电话询问 你以前的经验呢？
That's right there,see? The manager,Chandler Bing?
就写在下面了 我经理叫做钱德宾
All right.
好吧
Let's see if you're as good in person as you are on paper. Make me a salad.
来看看你是不是跟你写的 一样好，做一份沙拉来瞧瞧
A salad? I could do something more complicated.
沙拉？ 其实我可以做些难度比较高的
No,just the salad will be fine.
不用，沙拉就行了
You got it.
没问题
Now I want you to tell me what you're doing while you're doing it.
可是我要你一边做 一边告诉我你正在做什么
All right. Well, I'm tearing the lettuce.
好，我在撕生菜
Is it dirty?
菜脏吗？
Oh,I'm gonna wash it.
不…别担心，我待会儿会洗
Don't. I like it dirty.
别洗，我喜欢脏的
That's your call.
悉听尊便了
So,what are you going to do next?
好，你接下来要做什么？
I thought that l'd cut up the tomatoes.
我想，我接下来要切蕃茄了
Are they firm?
蕃茄结实吗？
They're okay.
还可以啦
You sure they haven't gone bad?
你确定蕃茄没坏？
You sure they're not very,very bad?
你确定没有非常非常的坏？
No,really,they're okay.
是啊，还可以啦
You gonna slice them up real nice?
你会切得很漂亮吗？
I was going to do them julienne.
事实上，我打算切成丝状
I'm out of here!
我走了
Hello?
喂？
Rachel's not here. Can I take a message?
不，瑞秋现在不在 你要不要留话？
How do we spell Casey?
好，哪个凯…哪个西…？
Is it like "at the bat" or "and The Sunshine Band"?
打棒球那个 还是乐团的那个？
Hey,who's this Casey?
这个凯西是什么人啊？
A guy she met at the movies.
她看电影认识的人
What does he want with her?
真的？他找她干什么？
I guess he wants to do a little dance...
我猜他想跟她跳点小舞…
...you know,make a little love....
…做一点小爱…
Well,get down tonight.
今天晚上就把她“解决”掉
I don't know. I don't
我不知道，我不懂…
I don't get it! Two months ago, Rachel and I were this close.
两个月前 我们就差这么一点点了
Now I'm taking messages from guys she meets at the movies?
现在呢 我在替她看电影认识的人留言
I mean,this Casey should be taking down my messages,you know?
应该是 这个凯西替我留言才对呀
Or Rachel and I should be together...
或…或是… 或是我跟瑞秋应该在一起…
...and we should get some kind of message service.
…然后我们… 我们一起请电话秘书
Hang in there. It's gonna happen.
耐心点吧，会有那一天的
Now,how do you know that?
好，你怎么知道呢？
Because she's your lobster.
因为她是你的龙虾
Oh,she's going somewhere.
她有话要说的
It's a known fact that lobsters fall in love and mate for life.
谁不晓得龙虾一旦恋爱 就会白头偕老呢
You know what? You can actually see old lobster couples...
你真的可以看到老龙虾夫妻…
...walking around their tank, holding claws,like....
…在水缸里爪子牵着爪子散步
Hey,you feeling better?
好点了吗？
Yeah,I think that fifth shower got the interview off me.
我想我的第五次澡 终于洗掉那个面试了
Do you have other possibilities?
你还有其他的机会吗？
There is the possibility that I won't make rent.
有，我很可能会付不出房租来
If you want, I can lend you money.
摩妮卡，你要的话我可以借你钱
If I couldn't pay you back right away, I'd feel guilty and tense around you.
因为如果我没有办法马上还 看到你就会内疚跟紧张
Then why not borrow it from Mom and Dad?
好吧 那你为什么不跟爸妈借呢？
You feel guilty and tense around them already.
反正你看到他们 就会内疚跟紧张
Might as well make some money off of them.
还不如趁机会跟他们刮点钱
The man's got a point.
他说得很有道理
What is that sparkly thing?
什么东西亮亮的？
That thing?
那个？那个是…
Yeah,it's a little flashy.
是…有点俗气啦
No,no.
不俗气
No,no. It's not flashy. Not for a goodfella.
不会…对道上兄弟来讲不会
Man,that is sharp! That must have cost you quite a few doubloons.
够帅的 你一定撇了不少榔吧？
Hi,darling.
亲爱的
What's this?
这是什么？
Some of your old stuff.
你以前的东西
Well,sweetie, we have a surprise for you.
亲爱的，我们要给你一个惊喜
We're turning your room into a gym.
你房间要改成健身房了
Wow,that is a surprise!
的确是个惊喜
Just one question. Why not Ross's room?
只有个小问题 为何不挑哥的房间？
We talked about that...
那我们也讨论过了…
... but your brother had so many science trophies,plaques,merit badges....
…但你哥哥有那么多的科学奖杯 奖牌，还有优点勋章…
We didn't want to disturb them.
我们不想去惊动它们
God forbid!
老天也不准
We were so sorry to hear about your parents splitting up.
我们很遗撼你父母分开的消息
Well,they're just separated. You never know! We'll see.
他们只是分居 谁知道呢，看看吧
I can't say any of us were surprised.
老实说，我们一点也不惊讶
They've been unhappy ever since we've known them.
从我们认识他们开始 他们就一直很不快乐
Especially after that incident in Hawaii.
特别是在夏威夷那件事之后
What? What incident?
哪件事啊？
No,no. I must be thinking of someone else.
没什么啦… 一定是我想到别人去了
Maybe me!
或许是我
Don't you have some folding to do?
你不是要叠衣服吗？
Fold. You fold.
快去吧，去叠呀
-Want a refill? -I'm all right,thanks.
还要再加一点吗？ 不用了，谢谢
Give me a second. I want to get this just right.
你得再给我一点时间 我要学得逼真一点
Dude,eleven o'clock, totally hot babe checking you out.
老兄啊，十一点方向 有个惹火女O在看着你
That was really good. I think I'm ready for my penis now.
学得很不错 我想我可以去变性了
I know what you're thinking. Dave Thomas,founder of Wendy's.
我知道你在想什么 汤达夫温蒂的创办人，对吧？
I'm Gail.
我叫盖儿
I really have to go, but it was nice meeting you.
我真的必须走了 很高兴认识你
Excellent!
真是太好了
He could have gotten me a VCR or a set of golf clubs.
他可以送我录影机 或是一对高尔夫球杆也可以
But no! He got me the "woman repeller"!
但他就送了我一个 会吓走女人的东西
The eyesore from the Liberace House of Crap!
看了碍眼，戴了碍事儿
-It's not bad. -Easy for you to say.
没那么惨啦 对，你当然说得容易了
You're not sporting a reject from the Mr. Tcollection!
你又不用走来走去 炫耀怪头不要的东西
"l pity the fool that puts on my jewelry! I do! I do!"
“我可怜戴着首饰的笨蛋”
"l pity that fool"
“我可怜戴着…”
Hey,man! We were just doing some impressions.
兄弟，我们正在玩… 名人模仿秀呢
Do your Marcel Marceau.
表演你的马歇马叟
That's actually good.
模仿得很像呢
Would you look at that guy?
你看看那个砘
How long has he been talking to her?
他跟她已经说了多久废话了？
It's like,back off,buddy! She's a waitress,not a geisha.
滚开吧，兄弟 她只是服务生，又不是艺妓
I think she's okay.
我想她没有关系吧
Look at that!
你看看…
She pushes him away and he won't budge!
你看她把他推开，他还不滚
I'm gonna do something.
我要采取行动了
We'll get a condo...
我们可以在山上…
... right on the mountain. Ski in,ski out,it's great.
…租个公寓 滑进滑出，棒透了
Excuse me? Are you Rachel?
对不起，你是瑞秋吗？
What?
什么？
Ross Geller.
我叫盖勒罗斯
God,in your ad you said you were pretty,but wow!
广告里说你很漂亮，但是…哇
What are you doing?
你…你在干嘛？
Oh,my God,is this the wrong day?
老天，不是今天吗？
I don't believe it!
我真不敢相信
If it works out,we'll have something to tell the grandkids!
这件事如果成了的话 将来跟孙子们就有话讲了
You sure will.
对呀
I've gotta go.
对了，我该走了
Take care.
保重了
See you later.
慢走，再见
You're welcome.
不客气
-What? -I was saving you.
什么？ 我是在救你呀
Saving me from a pleasant conversation with an interesting man?
救我？让我不用 跟有趣的男人愉快地交谈？
From where I was
从我坐的那边看起来…
Okay,Ross,listen to me.
罗斯，你现在听我说
I am not yours to save.
我不是要你救的人
But you are.
但是你是呀
What?
什么？
You're my lobster.
你是我的龙虾
Are you being the blind-date guy again?
你知道吗？ 你又在装跟我盲目约会了
No,you're my lobster.
不…你是…你是我的龙虾
Lobsters....
龙虾…
In the tank,when they're old...
…在水缸里，老的时候
...they get with the They walk around holding the claws.
…它们会… 它们爪牵爪散步
In the tank! You know,with...
在水缸里…
...with the holding and....
…爪子牵着爪子…
Pheebs,you wanna help me with the lobster thing?
菲比，帮我解释一下 龙虾的事，好不好？
Do the claws again.
再表演一次爪子
Rach,forget the lobsters,okay?
瑞秋，忘了龙虾的事吧
Let's talk What about us?
我们…那我们呢？
Ross,there is no "us," okay?
罗斯，没有“我们”
No! Listen to me!
你听我说
I fell for you and I get clobbered.
我爱上了你，然后我受伤了
You then fall for me and I again get clobbered.
然后你爱上我 结果我还是受伤了
I'm tired of being clobbered,you know?
我受够了伤害
It's just not worth it.
根本就不值得
Well,but
但是…但…
No "but," Ross.
没有“但是”了，罗斯
We are never gonna happen,okay? Accept that.
我们是永远不可能的，接受吧
Except that what?
除非什么呢？
No. No.
不…
Accept that.
接受吧
Hey,man! Look,it's my best bud! How you doing?
老兄，你看，我的好兄弟 你怎么了？
You're getting good at that Marcel Marceau thing.
你这个马歇马叟 真是模仿得越来越好了
What do you say we play some ball? You and me,huh?
乔伊，我们去打球，怎么样？ 你跟我，你说怎么样啊？
Okay,that's my bad.
是我不好
If you hated the bracelet, you should have just said so.
你要是那么讨厌那只手镯 你应该直说就可以了
Doesn't the fact that I wore it...
我戴着这么讨厌的手镯…
...say how much our friendship means to me?
…那不就证明了我有多么重视 我们之间的友谊了吗？
But you insulted the bracelet and you made fun of me.
那你侮辱这只手镯 还有你嘲笑我的那件事呢？
Well,that's the part where I'm a wank.
所以说，我是个混蛋嘛
I was hoping you wouldn't focus on that.
不过我希望 你不要往那个方向想，好吗？
Come on,man! I said I was sorry a hundred times.
你不要这样嘛 我已经向你道过一百次歉了
I promise,I will never take it off my...
我保证以后手镯不离…
...wrist.
…手
But if you want to stay in there and be mad...
如果你要留在那里生气的话…
...you just,you stay in there.
…那你就留在里面好了
You know what the
你知道吗？最…
I am here,on my knees...
我向你下跪了…
... holding up these couch cushions...
…我举着这些沙发垫子…
...as a symbol of my sorrow and regret.
…表示我对你的歉意还有悔恨
Much like they did in biblical times.
跟古时候的人一样
Though you may haveth anger now....
你现在虽然很生气…
You know,that Steffi Graf has quite a tush.
那葛拉芙的玻璃还不错啊
I'm just saying! It's right there!
说说而已嘛，就在电视上
Hey,guys.
各位
Hi,darling.
亲爱的
You didn't bring my grandson?
我孙子呢？你没有带他来啊？
He's at Carol and Susan's today.
不，他在…凯洛跟苏珊那儿
A woman in my office is a lesbian.
我公司有一个女同性恋
I'm just saying!
说说而已
Jack,look! There's that house paint commercial that cracks you up!
杰克，你看 你觉得很好笑的油漆广告来了
-Where have you been? -Emotional hell.
你到哪儿去了？ 人间炼狱
Did they lend you the money?
他们有没有借你钱？
No,I haven't asked them yet.
没有，我还没有开口
Come on,Monica,do it.
去呀，摩妮卡，说呀
Hey,you guys.
爸，妈
Monica has some news.
摩妮卡有事要找你们
So listen,I'm sorry I didn't tell you this before,but...
抱歉我以前没有告诉你们…
... I'm no longer at my job. I had to leave it.
…我现在…并没有在工作 因为我必须离职
Why?
为什么？
Because they made me.
公司的决定
You were fired? What are you gonna do?
你被炒鱿鱼 那你现在怎么办呢？
Judy,relax. This is our little Harmonica we're talking about.
茱蒂，放心啦 这可是我们的小妮妮宝贝儿
We taught her well.
我们教导有方
-Ten percent of your paycheck goes? -ln the bank.
薪水的百分之十上哪儿去了？ 存银行了
So she dips into her savings. That's what it's there for.
就是嘛，所以她在吃她的老本 存钱本来就是应急的
She's gonna be fine.
她不会有事的
If you need a little extra...
如果那些钱还不够用的话…
...you know where to find it.
…你知道哪里有钱啊
Anything larger back there?
有大张一点的吗？
I can't believe it!
我真不敢相信
Would you stop already?
你停一下，好不好？
Get out of the bitter barn and play in the hay.
不要再怨天尤人了，高兴一点
Oh,you're right. I should play in the hay.
你说得对，我应该高兴一点的
I just dropped $400 to replace a bracelet I hated to begin with.
忘了我刚才白花花的四百大洋 去买一个我恨的手镯这件事
Bring on the hay!
逗我开心啊
Hey!
嘿
I've got something that'll make you happy.
我这儿有个包你大乐的东西
Guess what Gunther found?
猜根特刚找到什么了？
Hey,now you have two!
你现在有两个了
Oh,now you have two.
What am I gonna do?
我该如何是好？
How come you have two?
你怎么有两个？
This one's for you.
这个是送你的
Get out!
少来了
No,I can't.
我没办法
I know how much this means to you...
我知道这对你的意义重大…
...and this is about more than jewelry.
…我也知道不只是首饰而已
It's about you and me and the fact that we're "best buds."
这是关于你跟我 还有我们是“好兄弟”
Is this friendship? I think so!
这叫友谊吗？我觉得应该是
Check it out! We're bracelet buddies!
我们是手镯兄弟
That's what they'll call us!
大家都会这样叫我们的
Okay,here you go. Pay me back whenever you like.
好了，拿去吧 随你什么时候还都可以
You have dinosaur checks?
你用恐龙支票？
You get your money and you learn something.
对啊，你不但得到钱 还可以学到一点东西
What's wrong with that?
这有什么不对的？
Nothing.
没什么…
Hey,you're a cheap-a-saurus!
你是小器龙
I'm kidding,I'm kidding. Thank you,I'm very grateful.
开玩笑… 谢谢，我很感激你
Hey,Mon,what is this?
摩妮卡，这是什么东西啊？
That's my bathing suit from high school. I was a little bigger then.
我高中时代的泳衣啊 那个时候比较胖
I thought they used that to cover Connecticut when it rains.
我还以为是康乃狄克州 雨天用的遮雨棚呢
Hey,what's on this videotape?
摩妮卡，这带子里有什么？
I don't know. Let's put it in.
不知道，问倒我了 放来看看
Over here,Jack. Okay.
这边，杰克
Rachel's coming up the path.
瑞秋穿着粉蓝色出来了
Doesn't she look pretty? Jack?
好漂亮，是不是？
Can you get this?
过来拍她
Oh,my God!
我的天啊
What is with your nose?
你鼻子怎么回事啊？
They had to reduce it because of my deviated septum.
我隔膜长歪了 不得已，只好去缩鼻了
Okay,I was wrong. That's what they use to cover Connecticut.
我错了 那才是康乃狄克州的遮雨棚呢
This is us getting ready for the prom.
知道这是什么吗？ 毕业舞会前的准备
We don't have to watch.
各位，我们不用看这个
Yeah,we do.
我们要看…当然要看
-Come on! -It's fun!
看嘛 很好玩的
Get a shot of Monica.
你有没有拍摩妮卡？
Where's Monica?
摩妮卡在哪儿？
Over here,Dad!
这里啊，老爸
Wait. How do you zoom out?
等一等，镜头怎么伸缩？
There she is!
拍到了
Some girl ate Monica!
那个女的吃了摩妮卡
Shut up! The camera adds ten pounds.
闭嘴啦，上镜头会多十磅的
So how many cameras are actually on you?
那到底有几个镜头在拍你？
Oh,you look so great!
你好漂亮哦
So do you! You look beautiful!
你也是好美啊
-Oops. - What?
糟了 怎么了？
I think I got mayonnaise on you.
我想我的美乃滋沾到你了
Oh,it's just the shoulder, not my dress.
没关系啦 只是肩膀，没弄到衣服啊
Everybody smile!
你们笑一笑
Oh,Dad,turn it off!
爸，关掉啦
It is off.
关了
It is not! What's with the red light?
爸，你没关，那红灯亮着
It's the off light.
那表示关了
Right,Ross?
罗斯
Looking good,Mr. IKotter.
很帅嘛
- You look pretty tonight. -Oh,thanks.
你今天晚上很漂亮 谢谢
- What are you doing this summer? -I'm gonna hang out...
你今年夏天要做什么？ 你知道的，只是…
... work on my music.
…在家里待着玩我的音乐
Is my hook unhooked? These things keep falling down.
我钩子没钩吗？ 袖子一直掉下来，没办法固定
Let me see. I don't know.
我看看，不知道
What are you gonna do...
今年夏天你要做…
The guys are here!
他们来了
... this summer?
…什么？
Work on your music?
玩你的音乐？
Oh,my God! There's Roy Gublik!
天啊，你们看，是古洛伊耶
You know,Roy saw Star Wars 317 times.
洛伊看“昨际大战” 看了317次
He was in the paper.
他的名字还上了报
Where's Chip? Why isn't he here yet?
奇普呢？他为什么还没来？
He'll be here,okay? Take a chill pill.
他会来的，放心吧
There.
好了
I just told Rachel that Roy touched my boob.
我刚告诉瑞秋 洛伊摸我的咪咪
I can't go to the prom without a date. I can't! It's too late!
没男伴我去不成毕业舞会 来不及了
If you're not going, then I don't want to go.
你不去，我也不要去了
Oh,I'm gonna kick Chip's ass!
我要奇普好看
I have a wonderful idea.
我有个很棒的主意
You should take Rachel to the prom.
你可以陪瑞秋去参加舞会啊
Doubtful.
我很怀疑
Jack,give me that. Talk to your son.
杰克，那个给我 你跟儿子去谈一谈
All right,go on. This thing's heavy.
这玩意儿好重
Your mother's right. Take her. You can wear my tux.
你妈说得对，带她去 穿我的礼服
She won't wanna go with me.
爸，她不会想跟我去的
Of course she would! You're a college man!
她当然会，你是大学生呀
-I don't know. - Well,come on.
我不知道 去呀
Don't you wanna find out?
你不想弄清楚吗？
I can't believe I can't go to the prom!
真不敢相信 我去不成自己的毕业舞会
This is so harsh!
这太残酷了
-Hold my board. - Thataboy! Thataboy!
好，你帮我拿着 真有你的…
I think we've seen enough.
好了，各位，我想我们看够了
Let's turn it off.
我们把它关掉吧
Well,I'm not gonna watch.
那好吧，我就不看
Come on,kid. Let's go!
来吧，孩子，我们走了
-My! Are you handsome! -Let's show them!
天啊，你真帅 去给她们看看
Just a sec,Dad.
等一下，爸
Okay,be cool. Just be cool.
要酷…
Okay,Dad.
好了，老爸
Rachel,ready or not, here comes your knight in shining
瑞秋，准备好 你的白马王子来了
Oh,no.
糟了
Don't wait up!
别等我们回来了
Chip!
走了，奇普，快
Oh,dear!
天啊 哪一个？怎么按啊？
How do I turn this off?
杰克，这个怎么关啊？
Press the button.
按按钮
Which one? Which button? Jack!
哪个钮…？
The button! The button!
那个啦…
I can't believe you did that.
真不敢相信你那么做了
Yeah,well....
是呀…
See? He's her lobster!
瞧，他是她的龙虾
Dance with him!
跟他跳
Mom,I'm hungry!
妈，我饿了
Dance with your father.
跟你爸跳
I don't know any of your flashdances, but I'm no slouch on the dance floor.
我或许不会跳什么闪舞啦 不过我也绝不是个省油的灯
All right.
好吧
-Oh,Jack! -Oh,Judy!
杰克 茱蒂